...and then there was the time I found _____ on the root partition.
140 characters is just enough to explain _____.
_____ - the idiot's guide to _____ and _____.
_____ all the way down.
_____ as a service.
_____ dooms any project to epic failure.
_____ Driven Development.
_____ is a feature, not a bug.
_____ is for closers.
_____ is the new _____.
_____ is weaponized privilege.
_____ is webscale.
_____ or it didn't happen.
_____ with one weird trick.
_____, as one does.
_____, for some values of _____.
_____, is that even HA?
_____, the only thing worse than recruiting spam.
A sales rep just tried to pitch me on _____; I told them we already have _____.
Accidental _____.
After _____ came up, the retrospective really went downhill.
All that we had to do to halve our response times was implement _____.
Amazon built a datacenter on the moon to lessen the risk of _____ causing problems.
Apple just patented _____.
Ask Me Anything about _____.
But Google is using _____ so we should too!
Called on account of _____.
Chef convergence failed due to _____.
Continuous _____.
DevOps: Now with 100% more _____!
Did you know that we have _____ on pager rotation?
Disrupting the established players in _____ via _____.
Doge _____.
Employees must _____ before returning to work.
Enterprise _____ in the cloud.
Enterprise-ready _____.
Epic yak-shave caused by _____.
Etsy says we should _____ everything.
Every time someone brings up _____, I throw up a little in my mouth.
Facebook has acquired _____ for $10b and _____.
Free as in _____.
Glitter-bombed with _____.
Hi, I'm Troy McClure. You may remember me from such commit messages as _____ and _____.
How even is _____ formed?
I came up with an awesome regex that converts _____ to _____.
I can haz _____.
I don't own any jeans skinny enough to wear to a _____ meetup.
I ended up having to buy a replacement _____ on eBay.
I find Java to be way too much like _____.
I got paged at 3am because of _____.
I saw the best minds of my generation _____.
I think maybe I'll leave _____ off my resumé.
If _____ is the answer, you are asking the wrong question.
If we make this deadline, Management has promised us _____.
If you're _____, you're gonna have a bad time.
In order to improve security, we're upgrading to _____.
In the next planning session, we'll cover _____ and _____.
It figures - an article about our _____ was posted just as we're pivoting to _____.
It turns out that the button labeled "Don't Push" actually does _____.
It worked on my _____.
It's dangerous to go alone; take _____.
It's like trying to herd _____.
Last week, I created a Chef recipe for _____; this week, it's an entire cookbook for _____. Automation FTW!
Main benefits of automation: _____ and _____.
Management just told me I need to get certified in _____.
Management said it's OK to deploy _____ at 5pm on Friday
Marketing says we're leaders in the _____ space, but I think it's more accurate to say we specialize in _____.
My eyes started bleeding when I opened the editor and saw _____.
My Linkedin Endorsements include _____.
My next blog post will be about how we used _____ to create _____.
My two most indispensable tools are _____ and _____.
No route to host: _____.
Nobody ever got fired for buying _____.
Our app is like _____, but for _____.
Our competitive advantage is our _____.
Our entire app is geared towards providing _____.
Our greatest achievement in the last year is _____.
Our production backups are stored using _____.
Pour one out for _____.
Put some _____ on it
Restoring from backups failed due to _____.
RIAA is suing me for downloading _____.
Robots are going to make _____ obsolete.
Root cause of the outage? _____.
Running Windows in production leads to _____.
Security? We've got that! We use _____.
So, I was using Wireshark to check network traffic... Did you know we have _____ in production?
Sweet! I just found a Puppet module for _____!
The hardest problems in computer science are naming things, cache invalidation, and _____.
The Internet is for cat memes and _____,
The Internet of Things will be controlled by _____.
The most stable part of our infrastructure? _____
The only thing necessary for evil to triumph is _____.
The production datacenter burned down because of _____.
The status console is green, but I can't access _____.
The two pillars of our Continuous Deployment pipeline are _____ and _____.
There was no good solution for _____, so we built our own.
This account has exceeded the maximum number of _____.
This isn't going to be all unicorns and _____.
Time to schedule the postmortem for _____ .
To secure our next round of funding, Management says we need _____.
Uber is on surge pricing because of _____.
WARN: _____ has been deprecated.
We don't need _____ - we have _____ !
We really need to open-source our _____.
We replaced our _____ with _____.
We run production _____ and _____.
When I hooked the 3D printer up to the Internet, it accidentally created _____.
When I told Jez Humble about our _____, he actually cried.
When I was a kid we didn't have _____.
When I write a book about my experiences, it'll be called "_____, the good parts"
Who would have known that _____ could destroy an entire datacenter?
Will merge pull requests for _____.
Wrap it with the _____ duct tape.
xkcd.com just made a hilarious comic making fun of _____.
You know what our app needs? More _____, less _____.
You should think of your servers like _____ and not like _____.
Zero-day _____.